Peter Ehab

Web developer with 2 Years of experience, seeks employment as part of a dynamic and creative software development team.

Ali Saif ST, Sidi Bishr,
Alexandria, Egypt (willing to
relocate)
(+20) 0155 5840 994
petereroshdy@gmail.com

SKILLS

Understanding of **PHP** and **MySQL** application development with the knowledge of **Frontend** technologies, and familiarity with **MVC**, Plus understanding of open source projects such as **Wordpress**.

Experience in **Laravel framework**, With good experience in **Git**, Plus experience working with **Linux** environment.

Knowledge of **MySQL**, **PostgreSQL**, **MongoDB** and **Firebase** technologies.

Understanding of Third Party **APIs**, such Facebook, Google, Plus basic understanding of **Algorithms** and **Data Structure**.

Understanding of in Java Language and OOP paradigm.

Experience in **Android** Development.

EDUCATION

High Institute of Computer Science , Alexandria— IT *Degree* 2017 - 2021

PROJECTS

Github: https://github.com/peterehab1

EXPERIENCE

Backend at Fawaterk - 6 October, Egypt

June 2018 - September 2018

I was responsible for turning the code base for the platform from CakePHP to Laravel 5.6, plus adding new features.

Full stack developer freelancer at Upwork.com

April 2017 - June 2018

Building web apps and eCommerce based on PHP and Laravel Framework plus some tweaks in the Frontend sometimes.

LANGUAGES

Fluent in Arabic and English, Beginner in German